<resources>


    <string name="app_name">Manhwa Explorer</string>
    <string name="title_one">A Returner’s Magic Should Be Special</string>
    <string name="title_two">Omniscient Reader’s Viewpoint</string>
    <string name="title_three">The World After The Fall</string>
    <string name="title_four">The Greatest Estate Developer</string>
    <string name="title_five">The Wrath and the Dawn</string>
    <string name="title_six">Tricked Into Becoming the Heroine’s Stepmother</string>
    <string name="title_seven">The First Night With the Duke</string>
    <string name="title_eight"> Like Wind On A Dry Branch</string>
    <string name="title_nine">Everywhere and Nowhere</string>
    <string name="title_ten">Fluffy Boyfriend</string>

    <string name="creator_one">Usonan</string>
    <string name="creator_two">Sing N Song, Sleepy-C</string>
    <string name="creator_three">Sing N Song, Undead Gamja</string>
    <string name="creator_four">Lee Hyunmin, Kim Hyunsoo</string>
    <string name="creator_five">Renee Ahdieh</string>
    <string name="creator_six">Mokgamgi</string>
    <string name="creator_seven">Teava</string>
    <string name="creator_eight">Dalsaeowl</string>
    <string name="creator_nine">Merryweather</string>
    <string name="creator_ten">Mihi</string>

    <string name="reads_one">1.3B</string>
    <string name="reads_two">349.4M</string>
    <string name="reads_three"> 52.8M</string>
    <string name="reads_four">87.3M</string>
    <string name="reads_five">73.6M</string>
    <string name="reads_six">87.2M</string>
    <string name="reads_seven">110.1M</string>
    <string name="reads_eight">114.1M</string>
    <string name="reads_nine">102.8M</string>
    <string name="reads_ten">95.1M</string>







    <string name="brief_one">This adventure fantasy manhwa is a story about the apocalypse and human destruction through the eyes of Desir Arman</string>
    <string name="brief_two">Omniscient Reader’s Viewpoint delivers a post-apocalyptic experience filled with legendary and mythical lore.</string>
    <string name="brief_three">The apocalyptic adventure fantasy Manhwa The World After the Fall explores the fictional destruction of humanity in a world of supernatural powers. </string>
    <string name="brief_four">One of the best adventure fantasy manhwa, The Greatest Estate Developer, focuses on Suho Kim, a civil engineer who had a hard life because of bad financial conditions.</string>
    <string name="brief_five">The Wrath and the Dawn is a retelling of the Arabian Nights – One Thousand and One Nights Tale. </string>
    <string name="brief_six">We can’t talk about the best adventure fantasy, manhwa, and not recommend a few reincarnation stories.</string>
    <string name="brief_seven">The First Night With the Duke centers on Ripley, who is an extra in her favorite novel. She is a college student who one day wakes up in the body of a noblewoman.</string>
    <string name="brief_eight">Rieta is a widow on her way to being buried alive with the dead nobleman who took her hostage. </string>
    <string name="brief_nine">Following their death in Shakespeare’s tragic play Hamlet, William Rosencrantz and Anne Guildenstern find themselves transferred into the present day.</string>
    <string name="brief_ten">Fluffy Boyfriend is a true adventure fantasy manhwa as it deals with the love story of half-animal humans living in disguise in the human world.</string>


    <string name="detail_one">This adventure fantasy manhwa is a story about the apocalypse and human destruction through the eyes of Desir Arman. Being one of the six surviving humans of the destruction, Desir thinks there is nothing left but to die. And just at his death, he finds himself transported back thirteen years ago. Now, having this second opportunity, Desire is determined to alter the past. Read A Returner’s Magic Should Be Special to taste the blend of action, dark, and adventure fantasy manhwa.

</string>
    <string name="detail_two">Omniscient Reader’s Viewpoint delivers a post-apocalyptic experience filled with legendary and mythical lore. This dark fantasy manhwa focuses on Kim Dokja, who derives pleasure only from a particular book that he manages to finish. In a shocking turn of events, his life turns upside down when the fictional book becomes reality. Being the only one with complete knowledge of this world, he becomes the center of attraction of a lethal game.</string>
    <string name="detail_three">The apocalyptic adventure fantasy Manhwa The World After the Fall explores the fictional destruction of humanity in a world of supernatural powers. However, unlike an Isekai fantasy, this manhwa explores the possibilities beyond the destruction of humanity. It focuses on Jaehwan, who, like others, was summoned as Walkers into the Tower of Nightmares. Humanity’s hope and the chance to return in time now depend on him and what he will witness at the top of the Tower.</string>
    <string name="detail_four">One of the best adventure fantasy manhwa, The Greatest Estate Developer, focuses on Suho Kim, a civil engineer who had a hard life because of bad financial conditions. Suddenly, one day, he wakes up in a novel called Knight of Blood and Iron, which he had read the night before. Unfortunately for him, he ends up in the body of Lloyd Frontera, the eldest son of the Baron, who was known to be a troublemaker and drunkard. Determined to change his fate, he uses his skills as a civil engineer to make goods and buildings to free his family of their debt.</string>
    <string name="detail_five">The Wrath and the Dawn is a retelling of the Arabian Nights – One Thousand and One Nights Tale. Every day, the Caliph of Khorasan, Khalid marries a new woman, and by dawn, the bride gets killed. The other main character of the manhwa Shahrzad marries Khalid to seek vengeance for her best friend. She plans to stay alive murder the king, and put an end to the terror.

</string>
    <string name="detail_six">We can’t talk about the best adventure fantasy, manhwa, and not recommend a few reincarnation stories. Daisy is a woman with a kind yet strong personality. After dying in the real world, she wakes up in the novel she wrote with her 9 other friends just for fun. Unfortunately, her living conditions do not change much. However, one random day, she is arrested by the Duke’s soldier for helping her friend out. Read Tricked Into Becoming the Heroine’s Stepmother to know what happens to Daisy.</string>
    <string name="detail_seven">The First Night With the Duke centers on Ripley, who is an extra in her favorite novel. She is a college student who one day wakes up in the body of a noblewoman. She decides to watch the plot unfold from the sidelines while enjoying her new luxury life. However, one day, she wakes up in the bed of the Duke, who was infamous for being cold. Ripley finds herself at a loss for words, as the female lead, who was a commoner, was supposed to end up with the Handsome Duke. Why is the Duke acting too friendly with her when he is supposed to fall for the original female protagonist?</string>
    <string name="detail_eight">Rieta is a widow on her way to being buried alive with the dead nobleman who took her hostage. Lost all hope in life, as her husband died because of the plague while her daughter was taken by the slave traders. Suddenly, a young and beautiful man ends up saving her by paying for her and taking care of her. Turns out it was the prince who was cast aside from the main empire and lived in a faraway territory. Why is the prince so nice to her even though she is a widow? What is Rieta hiding from everyone? Did Rieta find her lost daughter?</string>
    <string name="detail_nine">Following their death in Shakespeare’s tragic play Hamlet, William Rosencrantz and Anne Guildenstern find themselves transferred into the present day. They quickly discover that they are immortal and can time travel to any period in history except for their original time. To get familiar with the present time, William and Anne decide to enroll themselves in an upper-class high school where they meet friends and foes and, try to fathom normal life.

</string>
    <string name="detail_ten">Fluffy Boyfriend is a true adventure fantasy manhwa as it deals with the love story of half-animal humans living in disguise in the human world. The story focuses on Niko, a human who retains cat ears and tails, and Anna, who has a special condition where butterflies come out of her body. Niko used to live in a laboratory; however, he has spent time in the human world, keeping his truth a disguise as Anna’s pet. the manhwa focuses on these two characters as they grow up together with their real identity.</string>
</resources>